Good thing it's sunny today, huh?
I'm Ohto Ai.
Your clothes are cute.
Where do you shop?
Really, though, the weather is great.
Isn't it hard to protect a lot of Eggs?
Is there a trick to it?
These snacks are really good.
Can I ask you a question, too?
Of course! Ask me anything!
Who are you fighting for?
For Koito, of course!
Who's Koito?
My friend.
I see.
Are you sure it's not for yourself?
What do you mean?
You don't like who you are now, so you go.
Even if you're scared.
You want to change the self you hate.
You too?
I'm not like you. I love myself.
Why do you do it, then?
For my sister.
Your sister?
I let her die.
I'm home.
Welcome home,
Ai.
Ohto,
do your injuries feel all right now?
Your mother is worried.
Won't you tell me what happened to you?
Ai!
Ma'am.
I'm sorry.
Do you hate me that much?
Not really.
I don't hate you.
I'm glad.
You can't say that!
Here's my contact info.
Message me when you want to change plans.
I'll buy Eggs on odd days; you buy them on even days.
Huh?!
We won't have to meet again.
Good luck.
Don't misuse my contact info.
As if.
So,
as long as I don't crack the Egg, nothing will happen.
They don't attack me, after all.
Okay.
Umm...
Sorry, talk later!
Huh?
Run!
Umm, what's going on?
Is this... a school?
Hey, where are you going?!
Ow...
You okay?
Hey, wait!
I'll protect you!
Thank you.
This way!
Go in there!
I think that should buy us some time.
Sorry to spring that on you. I'm—
Are you okay?
I'm Ohto Ai.
Suzuhara Minami.
Don't worry. I'll protect you to save Koito.
Koito?
She's your friend?
Yup.
I'm jealous.
I wish I had friends.
Huh?! Umm...
So, why a leotard?
Huh? Umm... I'm in the gymnastics club.
I knew it!
You've got a great figure. I'm jealous.
The coach was always yelling at me to maintain it.
I'm a shut-in, so my legs are all puffy.
You're a shut-in?
Yup. I'm hopeless.
Wow.
Huh?
I wish I had your spirit and guts.
Wh-What do you mean?
One time, I made up my mind to skip morning practice.
Yeah?
I wanted to stay in bed.
I know that feeling.
I wanted to see what morning rush hour was like.
Oh.
But, maybe because I psyched myself
up, I couldn't sleep all night.
Oh, yeah!
Like when you wake up and it's already evening!
In the end, I went to morning practice without sleeping.
I was out of it from my all-nighter,
so the coach really let me have it.
I think that's way more impressive than anything I do.
If only I were strong like you, Ohto.
Don't worry.
I'll protect you, so let's survive together.
Yes.
It will take more than that to bring your friend back.
Huh?
Oh, it's kind of...
Here I am. Over here.
To free the captured maiden,
you have to beat the Wonder Killer.
What does that mean?
I thought it would be easier
to understand if they had a name.
Don't we just have to survive?!
How is just running away supposed to solve anything?
Stand and fight, young lady!
Stand and fight what?
A Wonder Killer is the form of an Egg's trauma.
The two are drawn to each other.
To take down a Wonder Killer, you need...
your...
What?
U-Umm...
Hello?
I hear something from the other side of the...
Is that delinquent rubbing off on you?
I only took my eyes off you for a minute.
Who's this lady?
Practice. Don't slack off, Suzuhara.
Speak up!
I'm sorry, Coach!
C-Coach?!
This is her trauma?!
You mean my teaching? Nonsense.
Stay away from Minami.
Now I'm really—
No!
It's because I'm no good.
Huh?
That's right. It's because you don't have enough spirit.
I'm sorry. I'll try harder.
What do you mean?
Wasn't that so hard you couldn't take it?
Coach says she does it for me, because I'm gutless.
Mi...
Minami, get away from her!
I'll...
Minami...
Oh, no. What happened?
Classic harassment.
Why would they do this to you?
Because you're my friend?
That's not it.
They say Mr. Sawaki is giving me special treatment.
I think they're jealous.
Of course he is. You're a transfer student.
A woman's jealousy sure is scary, huh?
This isn't funny.
Hey, this is wicked.
Hey, face this way.
Please stop.
Hey.
Are you okay?
Did you get the video?
I'm sorry. I was scared.
Scared of being left out.
You were scared, huh?
Sorry.
I'm so sorry.
It's fine.
I know you tried your best.
I'm sorry.
I feel sorry for Minami.
What's so strong about you?
Shut up.
I'm going
to change.
That's what's wrong with you.
Your figure changed on your period?
Take gymnastics seriously, damn it!
I'm sorry. Please forgive me.
Just so you know, this isn't corporal punishment.
It's tough love. I do it because I love you.
Yes, Coach.
Once you're a good girl,
I'll make sure to finish you off painlessly.
Thank you very much.
Ohto?
Enough is enough, you old bitch!
Stop!
It's my fault!
Leave me alone!
I don't have enough spirit or guts, and I'm ugly and timid.
It's all my fault.
So...
So—
You just want attention!
What you really mean is that you
want someone to find you and love you!
So, I won't leave you alone!
I can't leave you alone!
Keep your mouth shut, brat!
Shut up, bitch!
You're interrupting practice!
You annoying fly.
Please stop, Coach!
I'll do what you say!
I'll do anything!
Minami...
Oh, for the love of...
You're all hopeless!
My ribbon.
All right!
I can fight with this!
How do you like this, then?
What is this stuff? I can't see.
It's over.
Jump!
Dodge right!
She'll come from behind!
What do you think you're doing?
Are you disobeying me?
Are you going to betray me?
Betray my tough love?
I won't know if you don't speak up!
Well? Are you going to disobey me?
Answer me, Suzuhara!
Here. I'm right here.
Stupid brats!
I've got clout with the association!
They even consult me
when they pick competitors!
So...
So what, you asshole?!
It's tough love!
Dodge!
Sorry, but that's just abuse!
Now I'm really mad!
Goodbye, Coach!
Minami!
Are you okay?!
Thank you, Ai.
It's thanks to you and your ribbon.
You were really brave.
Yeah.
I wish I'd met you sooner, Ai.
If I had, we'd have chatted over
burgers and played games and things.
Like normal girls.
Yeah.
Will you remember me sometimes?
Minami?
Damn it.
Is one enough for you?
You're prudent, unlike Neiru.
Haste makes waste.
Did she die?
I don't know.
There's no point going to save
someone if she gets herself killed.
What do you know about it?!
It's her sister.
Neiru is going to save her little sister.
She wants to save her quickly.
I wonder about that.
Maybe she really wants to die, too.
Huh?
That's why she's fearless.
What are you doing?
Oh, sorry.
Are you recovering okay?
I guess.
I'm glad.
What would we do if we were friends?
We could go to a burger place.
And then what?
You and I would eat.
Fries, burgers, that kind of thing.
We'd both eat them together, at the same table.
Is that fun?
I wonder.
Here.
Thanks.
This smells amazing!
You're right.
Right?
Maybe once in a while.
Hm?
To be continued.